Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Latin America Serials TAM.770
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Latin America Serials
1937-2008
1960-1999
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
TAM.770
10.7 Linear Feet in 17 manuscript boxes and 13 flat boxes
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Latin America Serials contains over 250 titles published in Latin America, the United States, and other countries on politics, social issues, and culture in Latin America in the 20th century. The collection dates between 1937 and 2008, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1960s through the 1990s. Topics include civil wars and revolutions in Central and South America between the 1960s and the 1980s, immigration and refugee issues, communism in Latin America, and United States intervention in the region in the 1970s and 1980s.
Arrangement
Serials in this collection are arranged alphabetically by title.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection combines serials relating to Latin America drawn from two discrete groups of material held by the Tamiment Library. The first was a partially inventoried backlog of serials, received by the library through donations, subscriptions, and in archival collections. The second group consisted of around 1,700 serials, newspapers, and magazines, organized by title as an artificial collection, referred to as Periodicals.001 or Boxed Newspapers. This material was combined, inventoried, and arranged and described in subject-based categories in 2017. The accession number related to this collection is 2017.049.
Scope and Contents
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Latin America Serials contains over 250 titles published in Latin America, the United States (US), and other countries on politics, social issues, and culture in Latin America in the 20th century. The collection dates between 1937 and 2008, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1960s through the 1990s. Topics include civil wars and revolutions in El Salvador, Nicaragua, Guatemala, and Colombia through the 1960s and 1990s; immigration and refugee issues in New York and Florida; and United States intervention in the region in the 1970s and 1980s. The majority of the collection focuses on Central and South America, but some serials focus on issues in Haiti, the West Indies, Grenada, and Jamaica and issues relating to emigrants from those islands. Other topics include issues surrounding Cuban immigrants and refugees in the US and communism in Latin America. Large runs include Latin American Perspectives and Unidad Latina.
Communism -- Cuba.; Cuba -- History -- 20th century.; Latin America -- Politics and government -- 20th century.; Latin America -- Relations -- United States.; Serials (publications); El Salvador -- Politics and government -- 1979-1992.; Caribbean Area -- Politics and government.; National liberation movements -- Latin America -- History.; Civil War -- Latin America.
- 1984: At 50 Years...Sandino Lives: Commemoration of the 50th Anniversary of the death of General Augusto C. Sandino: May 19th Communist Organization, Chicago, IL (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Abdala Newsletter: Abdala Cuban Movement, Coral Gables, FL, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Abigarrada: Abigarrada, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Accion Libertaria: La Federacion Libertaria Argentina, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Accion Libertaria: Regional de Asturias y Leon, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
- Action Alert: Central America Peace Campaign, Spokane, WA, 1987-1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Agrarian Reform in El Salvador: A Program of Rural Pacification: EPICA Task Force, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Ahora: Ahora, Alamosa, CO, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1, Box 12, Folder 12)
- AL Taller (Taller Latinoamericano): The Latin American Workshop, Inc., New York, NY, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Alert!: Focus on Central America: Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador, Washington, DC, 1984-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1-7, Box 29, Folder 2)
- Altercom: Instituto Latinoamericano de Estudios Transnacionales, Santiago de Chile, Chile, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- America Latina-Derechos Humanos: Cencos, Mexico, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Anexos Boletin: Comite Chileno de Solidaridad, Havana, Cuba, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Areito: Areito, Inc., Miami, FL, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Arquitectura Cuba: Colegio Nacional de Arquitectos, Havana, Cuba, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Artes Plasticas: Ministerio de Educacion, Havana, Cuba, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Asi Trabajo Yo: Quimanto, Santiago, Chile, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- ATLAS: ATLAS, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Aztlan: Aztlan Publications, Los Angeles, CA, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Bandera Socialista: Partido Revolucionario de las y los Trabajadores, Mexico City, Mexico, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 1, Box 29, Folder 3)
- Baragua!: National Network on Cuba / DC "Hands Off" Cuba Coalition, Washington, DC, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Barricada: Sandinista National Liberation Front, Managua, Nicaragua Libre, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5, Box 12, Folder 18)
- Barricada Internacional: Sandinista National Liberation Front, Managua, Nicaragua, 1984-1990 (Box 2, Folder 6-9, Box 29, Folder 4)
- Barricadita: Casa Nicaragua, New York, NY, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Basta Ya!: Los Siete de la Raza, San Francisco, CA, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 2-5)
- Basta!: Central America Solidarity Committee, Baltimore, MD, 1991-1994 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Bioestadistica: Centro Nacional de Informacion de Ciencias Medicas, Bogota, Colombia, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Biografia del Personaje: Publicaciones Cruz O.S.A., Mexico City, Mexico, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Bohemia: Federacion de Mujeres Cubanos, Cuba, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Boletim IBASP: Instituto Brasileiro de Amizade e Solidaridade aos Povos, Recife (PE), Brazil, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Boletim Sei: Sociedade de Estudos Onteramericanos, Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Boletin: Departamento de Relaciones Publicas, Havana, Cuba, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Boletin: Chile en Lucha, Chicago, IL, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Boletin Cultural: Ministerio de Relaciones Exteriores, Cuba, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Boletin de la Alianza Internacional "Giuseppe Garibaldi" por la Libertad de Italia: Alianza Internacional "Giuseppe Garibaldi", Mexico City, Mexico, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Boletin Informativo: Comite Central del Partido Comunista de Chile, Santiago, Chile, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 10, Box 14, Folder 1)
- Boletin Informativo: Comite Chileno de Solidaridad con La Resistencia Antifascista, Havana, Cuba, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 4-9)
- Boletin Informativo: Chile Democratico, Rome, Italy, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Boletin Informativo: La Izquierda Chilena, Coordinador en el Exterior, Rome, Italy, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Boletin Informativo: Chile Antifascista, Berlin, Germany, Undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Caribbean Patriot: West Indian Progressive Study Group, Undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Casa: Casa de las Americas, Habana, Cuba, Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Casa Chile Human Rights Bulletin: Casa Chile, Berkeley, CA, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Casa Chile Update: Casa Chile, Berkeley, CA, 1983-1985 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Casa de las Americas: Casa de las Americas, Havana, Cuba, 1968-1981 (Box 14, Folder 7-9, Box Shared Tamiment 050, Folder 2)
- CCS Newsletter: Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Center for Cuban Studies Newsletter: Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Central America in the Classroom: Network of Educators' Committees on Central America, Washington, DC, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Central America NewsPak: Central America Resource Center, Austin, TX, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Central America Report: Central America Education Fund, Cambridge, MA, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Central America Report: Religious Task Force on Central America, Washington, DC, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Central America Report: Inforpress Centroamericana, Ciudad de Guatemala, Guatemala, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Central America Reporter: Central America Education Fund, Cambridge, MA, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Chile: Correspondents of the Underground Newspaper "Unidad Antifascista", Chile, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Chile Alert: Chile Alert Network, Washington, DC, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Chile Bulletin: Commission on Human Rights Secretariat in Solidarity with Chile, New York, NY, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Chile Democrático: Chile Democrático, Rome, Italy, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 7, Box 15, Folder 3)
- Chile en la Resistencia: Comite Chileno Antifascista, Mexico City, Mexico, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Chile Gram: Chile Gram, Santiago, Chile, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Chile Net: Chile Information Network, New York, NY, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Chile Newsletter: Comite de Chilenos por la Democracia, Seattle, WA, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Chile Solidarity: Chile Solidarity Committee, New York, NY, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Chile Vencera: National Coordinating Center in Solidarity with Chile, New York, NY, 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 5, Box 24, Folder 4)
- Chile-America: Documentation and Research Center, Rome, Italy, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- CISPES New York Newsletter: Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador, New York, NY, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- CLASP Bulletin: Caribbean and Latin America Solidarity Project, New York, NY, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Colombia Rebelde: Colombia Rebelde, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Companero: Ejercito Guerrillero de los Pobres de Guatamala, Guatemala, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Conozca a Cuba por Cuba Internacional: Instituto del Libro, Havana, Cuba, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Consejo de Estado / Consejo del Pueblo: Consejo de Estado / Consejo del Pueblo, Nicaragua, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Contact-0: Instituto Latinoamericano de Estudios Transnacionales, Santiago, Chile, 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Contracultura: Underground Press Syndicate, Liberation News Service y Cosmic Circuit, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Contragate Alert: The Christic Institute, Washington, DC, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Cuadernos: Revista Cubana de Avance Cultural, Miami, FL, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Cuadernos Casa de Chile: Casa de Chile en Mexico, Mexico City, Mexico, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Cuadernos de Humanidades No. 14: Universidad Nacional de Salta, Salta, Argentina, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Cuadernos del Hombre Libre: Cuadernos del Hombre Libre, Miami, FL, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- CUBA: The Guardian, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Cuba: Cuba Revista Mensual, Havana, Cuba, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Cuba: Cómo se Construye la Esclavitud Proletaria: Frente Obrero Revolucionario Democrático Cubano (FORDC), Miami, FL, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Cuba: Fading Star in the Caribbean: Aspect Foundation, Inc., New York, NY, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Cuba: Revista Menusal: Cuba: Revista Menusal, Havana, Cuba, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
- Cuba Resource Center Newsletter: Cuba Resource Center, New York, NY, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 25, Box 24, Folder 16)
- Cuba Revolution et Culture: National Council of Culture, Havana, Cuba, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Cuba Si: Cuba Solidarity Campaign Magazine, London, UK, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Cuban Foreign Relations: Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Desfiladero: Desfiladero, Mexico City, Mexico, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Direct Solidarity: The Spirit of Magon Direct Solidarity Committee, New York, NY, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Dissent Paper on El Salvador and Central America: Overview Latin America, Cambridge, MA, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Economia y Desarrollo: Instituto de Economia de la Universidad de la Habana, Havana, Cuba, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
- Ediciones: Comite Central del Partido Comunista de Cuba / Editora Politica, Havana, Cuba, 1968-1983 (Box 16, Folder 13-15, Box 17, Folder 1)
- El Foro del Pueblo: Editorial Prensa Sembradora, Los Angeles, CA, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- El Hombre y el Trabajo en America: Union Panamericana, Washington, DC, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- El Independiente: Centro de Medios Independientes de Nueva York, New York, NY, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- El Reportero: El Reportero, San Francisco, CA, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- El Salvador: Refugees in Crisis: Salvadorean Humanitarian Aid, Research, and Education Foundation, Washington, DC, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- El Salvador Bulletin: U.S. - El Salvador Research & Information Center, Berkeley, CA, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- El Salvador Labor Report: Federation of Independent Associations & Unions of El Salvador, Washington, DC, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- El Salvador Newsletter: El Salvador Newsletter, Washington, DC, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- El Salvador Senal de Libertad: Radio Venceremos, Mexico City, Mexico, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- El Salvador Watch: Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES), Baltimore, MD, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- El Salvador Weekly Review: FMLN Documentation & Investigation Center, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- El Salvador's Link: Casa El Salvador, Farabundo Martí, New York, N.Y., 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
- El Siglo: Publicaciones El Siglo S.A., Santiago de Chile, Chile, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- El Tecolote: El Tecolote, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
- El Tornillo: El Tornillo, Mexico City, Mexico, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- El Young Lord: The Young Lords, Milwaukee, WI, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Encuentro: Latin American Institute, University of New Mexico, Albuquerque, NM, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Facts and Figures: Inter-American Regional Organization of Workers, Puerto Vallarta, Mexico, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Fidel Castro Main Report: Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- FMLN / FDR: CISPES (Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador), Washington, DC, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 7, Box 24, Folder 6)
- Folletos Populares: El Instituto Historico Centroamericano, Managua, Nicaragua, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 4, Box 24, Folder 7)
- Free West Indian: West Indian Company, St George's, Grenada, 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 1-5, Box 7, Folder 1-4)
- Friends for Jamaica Caribbean Newsletter: Friends for Jamaica, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Friends of A.M.E.S.: Women's Association of El Salvador, Seattle, WA, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Fuera De Linea: Fuera De Linea, San Diego, CA / Tijuana, Mexico, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Futuro: Universidad Obrera de Mexico, Mexico, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Grito y Fusil: Center for Information on Latin America, Quebec, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Guatemala Network News: Network in Solidarity with the People of Nicaragua, Washington, DC, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Guatemala Update: The Guatemala Solidarity Committee (GUASO), Seattle, WA, 1985-1987 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Guevara's Guerilla Strategy: A Critique and Some Proposals: Pathfinder Press, Inc., New York, NY, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Haiti Insight: A Bulletin on Refugee and Human Rights Affairs: National Coalition for Haitian Refugees, New York, NY, 1990-1996 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Haiti News Digest: Haiti Communications Project, Boston, MA, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Haiti progres: Haiti Progres, Brooklyn, NY, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Haiti Support Network Update: Haiti Support Network, New York, NY, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Hemispherica: U.S. Committee of the Inter-American Assn. for Democracy and Freedom, New York, NY, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Historia Unisinos: Universidade do Vale do Rio Dos Sinos, Sao Leopoldo, Brazil, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Hope in Chile: Bay Area Ecumenical Committee of Concern for Chile, San Francisco, CA, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Hoy: Hoy, Santiago, Chile, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Huracán: Alliance for Cultural Democracy, Minneapolis, MN, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Hydro Focus: A Fortnightly People's Newspaper Produced by and for the Hydro Region Workers and Residents: Upper Mazaruni Development Project, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- In Commemoration of the 50th Anniversary of the Assassination of General Augusto C. Sandino: Centro de Comunicacion Internacional, Managua, Nicaragua, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Incredible Rocky: North American Congress of Latin America (NACLA), Berkeley, CA, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Information from Cuba: Luis A. Reyes, New Delhi, India, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Inter-American Labor Bulletin: Inter-American Regional Organization, Washington, DC, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 11, Box 11, Folder 10)
- Interamericana: Organizacion Regional InterAmericana de Drabajadores, Mexico City, Mexico, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Interconnect: Interconnect, Pittsford, NY, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Internacionalismo: Direccion Internacional de la Tendencia Cuartainternacionalista, Lima, Peru, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Interpretacion del Anarquismo: Editorial Tierra y Libertad, Caracas, Venezuela, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- JR Juventud Rebelde: La Habana, Havana, Cuba, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Juventud Rebelde: Juventud Rebelde, Havana, Cuba, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 2-3, Box Shared Tamiment 054, Folder 4)
- La Causa: National Brown Beret Organization, Compton, CA, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- La Intervencion castrista en Venezuela: Distribuidora Universal, Miami, FL, Undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
- La Nueva Bandera: Movimiento Popular Peru, Queens, NY, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- La Palabra: Latin American Solidarity Committee, Ann Arbor, MI, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- La Palma: Una Esperanza Para La Paz: Comision Politico-Diplomatica del FMLN-FDR de El Salvador, El Salvador, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- La Verdad: La Verdad, San Diego, CA, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- La Voz del Quetzal: Association in Solidarity with Guatemala, Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- La Voz Latina: Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, Washington, DC, 1986-1992 (Box 18, Folder 20, Box 23, Folder 17)
- Labor Report on Central America: Labor Network on Central America, Oakland, CA, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Lambi: Lutte Revolutionnaire du Peuple Haitien, Haiti, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- LASA Newsletter: Latin American Studies Association, Austin, TX, 1979-1982 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Latin America Update: Washington Office on Latin America, Washington, DC, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Latin American Left: Westview Press, Boulder, CO, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Latin American Monitor: Latin American Monitor Ltd., London, UK, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Latin American Perspectives: Sage Publications, Inc., Newbury Park, CA, 1974-2005 (Box 25, Folder 1-6, Box 26, Folder 1-7, Box 27, Box 28)
- Latino: Latino, New York, NY, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Legislative Update: Washington Office on Latin America, Washington, DC, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Liberacion: Liberacion, New York, NY, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Los Terremotos Chilenos: Nosotros los Chilenos: Quimanto, Santiago, Chile, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Lucha: Christians Concerned for Chile, Notre Dame, IN, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Lucha Sandinista: Frente Sandinista de Liberacion Nacional (FSLN), Nicaragua, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Lucha!: National Network in Solidarity with the Nicaraguan People (NNSNP), National Network in Solidarity with the People of Guatemala (NISGUA) and the Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES), Washington, DC, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Lunes de Revolucion: Lunes de Revolucion, Havana, Cuba, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 10-13)
- Magisterio: Sindicato Nacional de Trabajadores de la Educacion, Mexico City, Mexico, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Marxismo Militante: Editorial Roalva, La Paz, Bolivia, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Memoria: Centro Cultural Pablo de la Torriente Brau, Havana, Cuba, 1998-2001 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Memorias de la Sierra Maestra: Jose Pardo Llada / Editorial Tierra Nueva, Havana, Cuba, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Ministerio de Estado Departamento de Prensa Poletin: Cuban State Department, Havana, Cuba, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- MX Sin Fronteras: MX Sin Fronteras, Chicago, IL, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- National Guard in Central America: National Guard Clearinghouse, St. Louis, MO, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- New York NICANEWS: Nicaragua Solidarity Network of Greater New York, New York, NY, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- New York Nicanews: NY Nicaragua Solidarity Network, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- News from Guatemala: News from Guatemala, Toronto, Ontario, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Newsletter: Council for Human Rights in Latin America, Eugene, OR, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Newsletter: Casa Chile: Seattle, Seattle, WA, 1987-1991 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Newsletter: West Side Committee for Friendly Relations with Cuba, New York, NY, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Nica Text: Nicaragua Technical Aid Group, Seattle, WA, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Nicaragua - Info fur die Solidaritatsarbeit in den Gewerkschaften: DGB-Jugend, Frankfurt, Germany, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Nicaragua Center for Community Action: SF Women's Centers, San Francisco, CA, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Nicaragua Libre: Nicaragua Libre, Germany, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Nicaragua Network News: Nicaragua Network, Washington, DC, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Nicaragua Support Project: New York Committee for Education, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Nicaragua: A People's Revolution: EPICA (Ecumenical Program for International Communication and Action) Task Force, Washington, DC, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Nicarauac: Ministerio de Cultura, Managua, Nicaragua, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- NICMAC Update: Nicaragua Medica / Material Aid Campaign, New York, NY, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Noticias de Colombia: Comite Central del Partido Comunista de Colombia, Bogota, Colombia, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 18, Box 24, Folder 9)
- Noticias de Colombia: Partido comunista de colombia, Bogota, Colombia, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Noticiero Argentino: Noticiero Argentino, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Novedades de la ANCE: La Oficina Latino-Americana de la ANCE en Buenos Aires, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Nueva Revista Cubana: Direccion General De Cultura, Havana, Cuba, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 19, Box 24, Folder 12)
- Organizacion Obrera: Federacion Obrera Regional Argentina, Argentina, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- OSGUA Newsletter: Organization in Solidarity with the People of Guatemala, Chicago, IL, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- PACCA: Policy Alternatives for the Caribbean and Central America, Washington, DC, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Palenque: Grupo Palenque, Coral Gables, FL, 1990-1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Patria: La Editorial Tropico, Havana, Cuba, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Peasant: Mouvman Peyizan Papay Education and Development Fund, Boston, MA, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Peasant: The Peasant Movement of Papay Education and Development Fund, Boston, MA, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- PEL: Panorama Economico Latinoamericano: Prensa Latina, Havana, Cuba, 1964-1968 (Box 20, Folder 6, Box 24, Folder 14)
- Pensamiento Critico: Pensamiento Critico, Havana, Cuba, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 9-12, Box 21, Folder 1)
- Pensamiento y Accion Marxista Leninistas en America Latina: Los Partidos Marxista - Leninistas de Colombia, Chile, Ecuador y Brasil, Brazil, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Plan 1000: A Strategy of Psychological Warfare in El Salvador: Radio Venceremos System, San Francisco, CA, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Plenty News: Plenty Staff, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)